Hello everyone my name is Rahul what is the geography of
unit manager of ICC Prudential Life Insurance
and
what is his salary which ones can
apply whether there is a field visit in it
or not we will
discuss all these things in detail in this video
ICC Prudential Life Insurance is
a subsidiary company of ICC Bank
which deals in your insurance
so first let's talk about the eligibility criteria of unit manager
so
who can apply for it if you have completed your
graduation or your post graduation then
you can apply for it
and there is no such percentage mentioned in it
that your marks should be 50% or 55%
you can have any percentage if you have passed
your graduation then you can apply for it
and if you have not completed your graduation,
you have only passed 12th then also you can
apply once from now because
in some states there is a criteria
12th pass is also accepted but it
depends on you that for which city or
which state the criteria is, then when you
apply at that place, it will be
shown to you in the description there and if you have done your graduation
or post graduation from any stream, be it
B.Com, B.B. or
B.Tech or anything, M.Tech or
anything, then also you can apply from now,
people from any stream can apply for it, so
now let's talk about how you
can apply or what is its experience
required, so even if you are unemployed,
you can apply for it and if you have
experience, then these people
also take up to a maximum of 8 years of experience
and this experience of yours
depends on which state you are
applying in, state wise its
criteria varies, so
when you apply, it will be
shown to you in the description there and this  To
apply for the post, you
can apply online in two ways, by going to the career portal
or you can also apply from naukari.com or
hindi.com or indian.com
and what happens in the other
method is that those people themselves
call you to see if you are interested
or not for the role of Major, then if they call
you then you can join from there also,
but now talk to them about the
enrolment or off-roll because
sometimes you are also hired on third party portal,
okay, so now let's talk about
its salary, what is its salary, its
minimum salary means
if you do not have any experience then
your minimum salary will be
2.15 lakh per month, that is,
if your
experience is from zero to one year, then the
salary that will be provided to you will be 2.65 lakh per month out of
2.15 lakh per month
You will be given maximum and if your
experience is more than one year, the
more your experience will be,
accordingly you will be provided salary,
its maximum salary goes up to ₹8 lakh per
annum, well it depends on your
state to state and on your
experience and your qualification
and there are many posts in ICC Bank Prudential Life
Insurance, there is
not only the post of Vineet Major,
there is also the process of your Product Manager or
Manager, but
we will talk about that in some other video,
in this video we will talk only about the Unit
Manager, so now let's
talk about its role, its role is that you have
got your
sales profile and in this the
product in which you deal is your
insurance, that is your life
insurance, general insurance, vitamin
insurance, all these insurances are there
and in this profile your main
daily visit is there, daily sales visit is there,
daily field visit is there, you have to
sell various insurances on
a target base, so in this you get
monthly  You also have to achieve the target,
so if I talk about the description in detail, then in this
you have to recruit and
identify your
high quality advisor and who is this advisor,
it can be your doctor, nurse or
advocate, anyone. Big
advisors basically sell your insurance,
like if a
patient comes to a doctor, then he can insure him, that
means any doctor can become your advisor,
he will sell insurance to
your own clients or patients
and why will he do this, why will he sell, then
he is also given commission for that, so
your only work is that you
go and make advisors, you go and
talk to doctors, nurses, clients, people,
train them, they have to learn everything
and give them knowledge about the products,
then they sell, for which they are
also given commission and if
you achieve the target, then you also
get an incentive, so in this role you have to
make more advisors, like you will have to
talk to doctors and new clients
Everyone will become his training dog,
knowledge dog in the product department, after that you can make him
sales training dog in the sales department, that
doctor, nurse or advocate or whoever is
your advisor, he can provide you leads, they will provide
you leads and will
tell you to go and close the deal, so
how will the doctor, nurse etc. generate leads, so
you will have to help them in that too, you will have to
guide them, you will have to train them
and at the same time you will also have to
answer that whatever
products or services your advisor is providing to the customer, he is providing them after
analyzing the needs of the customer,
you will have to go and teach all these things to your advisor,
you will have to achieve every target, in this
you will have to generate sales on your own,
you will also have to make lead lines on your own,
your advisor will generate leads for you
but you will also have to sell on your own
and you will have to keep insuring
that whatever production services your advisor is providing, all of them
are correct and there are adequate
needs, so when all these roles are there,
unit manager  So just summarize its
role, then you have to share it with yourself,
you have to create new advisors, you have to
recruit new advisors,
train them,
give them knowledge, give such a stage to ten-ten,
give them guidance
so that they can generate leads and for this
your advisor also gets commission and
you get salary and incentive, so
this is completely a sales profile, in this
your target is relief, you have to achieve the mandate, so
if you target in this then
you get this incentive monthly, yearly or
quarterly, so
in this the more you sell,
the more liquid you
become as an advisor, the more incentives you will be
provided, so it is up to you to join,
if you want to join it then you
can join, I have
told you everything in detail, if you
want to join the banking center in future and if
you do not have any experience, then
what happens in the bank is that you have to
increase your experience  If it is preferred then you
can join it now, you can gain experience by doing one or two jobs,
after that
you can directly join the banking sector as well, so
how to apply for it, you have to
go to Google and search ICC Prudential
Life Insurance Careers, after that
you have to click on the previous link,
after that here you have to
select Plus, if you select Advisor
then you will become an Advisor, meaning you will work on a
commission basis, so you have to
click on Plus, and
you will get three filters at the top in which you
can search for Unit Manager and if you have
any location preference then you can search from that
or if you search directly then
all the locations will be shown to you, after that when
you go to the description then you will get
all the details of what you have
and what press record you have, how much
responsibility you will have, then you
can apply for it and apart from this I will also give
you the link to apply
in the description, so you can go from there also
Apply Kar Sakta Ho Thank You So Match Par
Watching TV Jo D Best And Take Care By
Jai Hind
[Music]